# Gregg Bellofatto || Software Developer

#### **ABOUT ME**

After working in the automotive industry for 17 years, a career change is something I wanted. Through networking, a connection planted a seed that I should become a software developer. After researching the industry, I decided it would be a great opportunity. Attending Carolina Code School has now become one of the best decisions I could have made. As a graduate, I look forward to using my newly learned skills to take on challenges as a software developer.

#### **WORK SAMPLES - ON GITHUB**

# On Deck -Click here to view video

ReactJS, Django, React Bootstrap, Django-REST-Framework, Twillio API, Heroku

Full stack application geared towards the person with a busy schedule and would like to play recreational sports in their free time.

Teams can post available positions as they are needed to fill their teams empty spots.

# Newspaper App

ReactJS, Django, React Bootstrap, Django-REST-Framework

A project that showed cased the ability to create a full CRUD application utilizing ReactJS and Django.

# **Pixel Perfect**

HTML and CSS

A project that showcased the ability to learn and understand HTML and CSS functionality.

#### **CONTACT INFO**



bellofattogregg@gmail.com



LinkedIn



**GitHub** 

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML & CSS
- ReactJS
- JavaScript
- Python
- Bootstrap
- Django

# PROFESSIONAL TRAINING / EDUCATION

#### Carolina Code School

August - November 2022 Software Development Immersive Course

**New Hampshire Technical Institute**Associates of Science in Accounting 2005

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

- Freelance Frontend Development
- Audi Greenville Service Advisor May 2018 - August 2022
- Big "O" Dodge Service Advisor December 2015 - May 2018
- Dyna Tune Automotive
   June 2005 August 2015